<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brenda Thng</title>
    <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brenda Thng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Resume</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/resume/test-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/resume/test-resume/</guid>
      <description>Johnny Coder          1 MyAddress email@example.com   MyTown 1000 @twitter_handle   MyCountry 1800 my-phone-nr    Education  2010-2014 (expected) PhD, Computer Science; Awesome University (MyTown)
Thesis title: Deep Learning Approaches to the Self-Awesomeness Estimation Problem
 2007-2010 BSc, Computer Science and Electrical Engineering; University of HomeTown (HomeTown)
Minor: Awesomeology
  Experience Your Most Recent Work Experience:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Updating Marketing Dashboard on Google Spreadsheets</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/projects/self-updating-marketing-dashboard-google-spreadsheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/projects/self-updating-marketing-dashboard-google-spreadsheets/</guid>
      <description>How I created an automated marketing dashboard on Google Spreadsheets Background Perhaps I should first provide some background/context on this project that I worked on. For those that don&amp;rsquo;t know, I am interning at a commercial real estate tech startup in NYC for a year as part of a school programme that my university provided.
So when I first entered my internship company, I noticed that sales/marketing data were all being tracked on Google Spreadsheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to Write About</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/posts/things-to-write-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/posts/things-to-write-about/</guid>
      <description> Personal NOC Reflections (goals achieved, things to improve on) Goals when I get back  Learning Can I be a data scientist? How I created a product analytics dashboard on flask (Tags: Flask, Python, Numpy, Pandas, Plotly)  gr </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brenda&#39;s Resume</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/resume/brenda-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/resume/brenda-resume/</guid>
      <description>View the PDF version here
Kai Ting Brenda THNG Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, Github, R
Interest: Business Analytics, Data science, Data visualization, Infographics, Marketing, Fitness
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE REONOMY, New York, NY, August 2017 - July 2018
Product Intern
 Create and maintain dashboards of all company processes Build web application dashboard for product analytics on Python/Flask backed by PostgreSQL, Mixpanel API (create feature audits, cohort analysis charts with Plotly, Numpy and Pandas) Create automated marketing dashboards on Google Spreadsheets with the use of Google App Script and API integrations with various marketing platforms (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction Post</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/posts/introduction-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/posts/introduction-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my legit first post Hello world, I have been wanting to start a blog for ages and today I finally got round to doing it, even though I really shouldn&amp;rsquo;t as I have so many other things on my plate at this moment. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I manage to put inside some time to do this anyway.
People around me kept telling me that I should start a blog or portfolio of some sort to keep track of my progress, and also to have something to show for in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post Brenda</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/posts/first-post-brenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/posts/first-post-brenda/</guid>
      <description>Hello Hugo world! No more excuses for having no blog or documentation now!
Help: Link to theme Start a Blog in 30 minutes with Hugo GoHugo.io Getting-started documentation
Deployment Sites Firebase Netlify
var s = &amp;quot;JavaScript syntax highlighting&amp;quot;; alert(s);  s = &amp;quot;Python syntax highlighting&amp;quot; print s  No language indicated, so no syntax highlighting. But let&#39;s throw in a &amp;lt;b&amp;gt;tag&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;.  https://highlightjs.org/static/demo/
Link to Markdown Cheatsheet
How to use hugo  to create a new post  hugo new posts/introduction-post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Analytics Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/projects/first-project-brenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/projects/first-project-brenda/</guid>
      <description>Task Using a Flask framework, I created a simple dashboard to analyse the product performance overtime. I made use of the Mixpanel API and access to the company&amp;rsquo;s database to retrieve and manipulate the data in order to create these charts.
Some key charts include: Feature Audit Charts, Cohort Analysis Charts, Stickiness Ratio, Engagement Metrics
Problems Faced 1. 2. 3.
Lessons learnt 1. 2. 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brenda-thng.netlify.com/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>